Cameron Morales

Software Developer

- 708-845-0107
- cam.morales93@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Camm66
- @ cameronmorales.com

A recent computer science graduate with 3+ years of academic programming experience, currently seeking an entry-level position. Eager to leverage a passion for mastering new techniques and technologies throughout the various design and development stages of your software solutions.

Education

2016-09 - 2019-06

DePaul University, Chicago IL

M.S. Computer Science

GPA 3.73 / 4.0

Areas of Study: Object Oriented Development, Software Architecture, Web Applications, DevOps, Quality Assurance.

2011-09 - 2015-06

Columbia College, Chicago IL

B.A. Audio Design & Production

GPA 3.71 / 4.0

Areas of Study: Live Sound Mixing, Studio Recording, Signal Processing, Sound Design/Synthesis

থ্য

Skills

- Languages: Java, Python, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Frameworks: Flask, Angular, React
- Software: Eclipse, Visual Studios, IntelliJ IDE, MSOffice
- Version Control (Git)
- Excellent Customer Service
- Strong Communication and Collaboration

Q

Certificates

2017-08

2018-08

- COMPTIA Security+ Certification
- Udacity Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree



Experience

2017-07 - 2018-08

Perishables Buyer

Whole Foods Market

Responsibilities:

- Ordered, replenished, and merchandised perishable products and participated in regional and national sales promotions.
- Maintained and monitored department spoilage, food bank, and transfer logs.
- Managed Yearly Comp of 20% during peak holiday season.
- Oversaw implementation of the new 'Order-To-Shelf' standard operating procedures.

2015-11 - 2017-07

Grocery Team Member

Whole Foods Market